question_data= [{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The word &quot;Inception&quot; came from the 2010 blockbuster hit &quot;Inception&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science: Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"&quot;Windows NT&quot; is a monolithic kernel.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The average woman is 5 inches \/ 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that was a Sega Genesis with a disc drive.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In 1967, a magazine published a story about extracting hallucinogenic chemicals from bananas to raise moral questions about banning drugs.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Board Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"There is a Donald Trump Board Game, which was made in 1989.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"&quot;Cube&quot;, &quot;Cube 2: Hypercube&quot; and &quot;Cube Zero&quot; were directed by the same person.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Several characters in &quot;Super Mario 64&quot; blink their eyes, including Mario himself.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Space Station 13&quot;,  the station has a clown aboard it.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]